A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, SG 1.40 (A2015) FA761
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, SG 1.40 (A2015)
2000-2014
1980-2015
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller Foundation
FA761
22.34 Cubic Feet 17 standard record storage boxes, R4443-R4459.
6 standard record storage boxes, R4443-R4448.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Project files transferred to the RAC by Rockefeller Foundation, 2015.
Arrangement
Records are primarily arranged by Program.
Records are arranged as received. Within folders, materials are primarily arranged in reverse chronological order.
Conditions Governing Access
Records 10 years old and older are open for research. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC.
Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) or audiovisual material (audio cassettes, VHS, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact a RAC archivist.
Separated Materials
Special Formats (audio, film, video, digital media, library materials, memorabilia, oversize, and photographic material) have been separated from the body of the collection. All pertinent items are assigned a unique separation number, as noted. Requests to access open special formats should reference the unique separation number.
Scope and Contents
Grant administration files and related material.
- AC.2015.018: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 2009-2014; AC_2015_018; 5.26 Cubic Feet 4 standard record storage boxes, R4443-R4446.; 4 standard record storage boxes, R4443-R4446.
  - RES, 2010-2014; AC_2015_018_1; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2011 RES 311 - AFRICAN CENTER FOR ECONOMIC TRANSFORMATION - TREND MONITORING AND HORIZON SCANNING FOCUSED ON WEST AFRICA, 2010-2014 (Box R4443)
  - SEG, 2011-2014; AC_2015_018_2; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2011 SEG 207 - PEOPLE UNITED FOR SUSTAINABLE HOUSING - COMMUNITY IMPLEMENTATION SUPPORT, GJGNY, 2011-2014 (Box R4443)
    - 2011 SRC 107 - CHARTER CITIES - PLAYBOOK FOR RESILIENT AND INCLUSIVE CITIES, 2011-2013 (Box R4443)
    - 2011 SRC 108 - SANTA FE INSTITUTE OF SCIENCE - RESEARCH AND ANALYZE DATASETS ON URBAN ISSUES, 2011-2013 (Box R4443)
  - THS, 2011-2014; AC_2015_018_3; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2011 THS 316 - INAFI BANGLADESH FOUNDATION - HEALTH MICRO INSURANCE, 2011-2014 (Box R4443)
    - 2011 THS 327 - HELINA (MALI) - 2011 AFRICA E-HEALTH CONFERENCE, 2011-2014 (Box R4443)
    - 2011 THS 338 - UNITED NATIONS FOUNDATION - mHEALTH INNOVATORS AWARD 2011, 2011-2012 (Box R4443)
    - 2011 THS 339 - JEMBI HEALTH SYSTEMS (SOUTH AFRICA) - GENERAL SUPPORT, 2011-2014 (Box R4443)
    - 2011 THS 341 - INDEPTH NETWORK (GHANA) - HEALTH CARE SERVICES IN GHANA AND VIETNAM, 2011-2014 (Box R4443)
    - 2011 THS 345 - JOHNS HOPKINS UNIVERSITY - HEALTH MARKETS RESEARCH, 2011-2014 (Box R4443)
    - 2011 THS 363 - NATIONAL HOSPITAL INSURANCE FUND (KENYA) - HEALTH INSURANCE SUBSIDY PROGRAM, 2011-2013 (Box R4443)
  - Bellagio Study and Conference Center (BEL), 2012-2013; AC_2015_018_4; 4.8 Cubic Feet 2 standard record storage boxes, R4443-R4444
    - 2012 BEL 302 - ALEXANDER APOSTOL - BELLAGIO CREATIVE ARTS FELLOW, 2012-2013 (Box R4443)
      Conditions Governing Access
      Restricted - Fellowships - Open in 2033
    - 2012 BEL 303 - JOSE ANGEL TOIRAC - BELLAGIO CREATIVE ARTS FELLOW, 2012-2013 (Box R4443)
    - 2012 BEL 305 - RESOURCE ALLIANCE LTD. (ENGLAND) - BC CONFERENCE: BRIDGING PHILANTHROPY AND DEVELOPMENT IN AFRICA AND ASIA, 2012-2013 (Box R4443)
    - 2012 BEL 306 - YOUNG-HAE CHANG - BELLAGIO CREATIVE ARTS FELLOW, 2012-2013 (Box R4444)
    - 2012 BEL 308 - DELOITTE CONSULTING - ART AND SCIENCE OF CONVENING GUIDEBOOK, 2012-2013 (Box R4444)
    - 2012 BEL 309 - POPTECH INSTITUTE - BELLAGIO-POPTECH FELLOWS PROGRAM, 2012-2013 (Box R4444)
    - 2012 BEL 310 - MCGILL UNIVERSITY (CANADA) - BELLAGIO CONFERENCE ON INNOVATIVE CONVERGENCE, 2012-2013 (Box R4444)
  - CAC, 2010-2014; AC_2015_018_5; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2012 CAC 302 - ASIAN DISASTER PREPAREDNESS CENTER (THAILAND) - CLIMATE IMPACT REDUCTION RESEARCH IN SUPPORT OF ACCCRN, 2010-2014 (Box R4444)
    - 2012 CAC 303 - ROSIE SJ GREN (UNITED KINGDOM) - DONOR ENGAGEMENT SUPPORT FOR ACCCRN PARTNERS, 2011-2014 (Box R4444)
    - 2012 CAC 304 - INTERNATIONAL INSTITUTE FOR ENVIRONMENT AND DEVELOPMENT (ENGLAND) - SIXTH CONFERENCE ON COMMUNITY-BASED ADAPTATION (Box R4444)
    - 2012 CAC 305 - VIETNAM INSTITUTE OF ARCHITECTURE, URBAN AND RURAL PLANNING - CAPACITY BUILDING, 2012-2013 (Box R4444)
    - 2012 CAW 301 - ABT ASSOCIATES - EVALUATION OF THE CAMPAIGN FOR AMERICAN WORKERS INITIATIVE, 2012-2013 (Box R4444)
  - CCP, 2012-2013; AC_2015_018_6; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2012 CCP 302 - ALLIANCE FOR CLIMATE PROTECTION - COMMUNICATIONS CAMPAIGN DEFENDING CLIMATE SCIENCE, 2012-2013 (Box R4444)
    - 2012 CCP 303 - CLIMATE CENTRAL, INC. - GENERAL SUPPORT, 2012-2013 (Box R4444)
  - CEN, 2011-2014; AC_2015_018_7; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2012 CEN 302 - SHACK/SLUM DWELLERS INTERNATIONAL (SOUTH AFRICA) - EXPLORATORY SDI PRACTICES IN HAITI, 2012-2013 (Box R4444)
    - 2012 CEN 303 - JANVIKAS (INDIA) - YOUTH INNOVATION AWARD, 2012-2013 (Box R4444)
    - 2012 CEN 306 - SOCIAL FINANCE - INNOVATION FORUM AWARD (Box R4444)
    - 2012 CEN 309 - FARM RADIO INTERNATIONAL (CANADA) - "FARMQUEST", TO ENCOURAGE FARMING PROFESSION FOR YOUTH IN MALI AND OTHER AFRICAN COUNTRIES, 2011-2013 (Box R4444)
    - 2012 CEN 311 - KOUNKUEY DESIGN INITIATIVE, INC. - ONLILINE INFORMATION PORTAL: IN NAIROBI, KENYA, 2012-2014 (Box R4444)
    - 2012 CEN 315 - AJIMA FARMS AND GENERAL ENTERPRISES NIGERIA LIMITED - DEVELOP A YOUTH AGRICULTURAL ENTREPRENEURS, 2012-2014 (Box R4444)
    - 2012 CEN 317 - CONTEXT PARTNERS - PILOT NETWORK ENGAGEMENT TOOLS, 2012-2013 (Box R4444)
  - CSD, 2012-2014; AC_2015_018_8; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2012 CSD 201 - CONSERVATION INTERNATIONAL FOUNDATION - DEVELOPING A SMALLHOLDER AGRICULTURE STANDARD, 2012-2014 (Box R4445)
  - EIN, 2010-2014; AC_2015_018_9; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2012 EIN 301 - CONTEXT PARTNERS - IMPACT OF INNOVATION IN SOLVING SOCIAL PROBLEMS (Box R4445)
    - 2012 EIN 302 - MCKINSEY COMPANY, INC. - SOCIAL IMPACT BOND US MARKET STUDY, 2012-2013 (Box R4445)
    - 2012 EIN 304 - AFRICAN TECHNOLOGY POLICY STUDIES NETWORK (KENYA) - FOSTERING SOCIAL INNOVATION, 2012-2014 (Box R4445)
    - 2012 EIN 305 - HOPE INSTITUTE (SOUTH KOREA) - ECOSYSTEM FOR SOCIAL INNOVATION IN ASIA, 2012-2013 (Box R4445)
    - 2012 EIN 307 - FORUM FOR THE FUTURE (ENGLAND) -SOCIAL IMPACT BOND INNOVATION IN U.S., 2012-2013 (Box R4445)
    - 2012 EIN 308 - ROOT CAPITAL - CATALYZE STRATEGY TO ACCELERATE SOCIAL AND ECONOMIC PROGRESS, 2012-2013 (Box R4445)
    - 2012 EIN 310 - PORTLAND PR INC. - STRATEGIC MEDIA AND COMMUNICATIONS CAMPAIGN AROUND SOCIAL IMPACT BONDS, 2012-2013 (Box R4445)
    - 2012 EIN 311 - USHAHIDI, INC. - DEMONSTRATION PROJECT, 2012-2013 (Box R4445)
    - 2012 EIN 316 - NONPROFIT FINANCE FUND - PAY FOR SUCCESS FIELD BUILDING, 2012-2014 (Box R4445)
    - 2012 EIN 317 - NESTA OPERATING COMPANY(ENGLAND) - INNOVATION CORE OFFERINGS, 2012-2014 (Box R4445)
    - 2012 EVA 302 - PACT INSTITUTE - SOUTHEAST ASIA COMMUNITY OF PRACTICE, 2010-2014 (Box R4445)
  - EVA, 2009-2014; AC_2015_018_10; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2012 EVA 305 - OXFAM AMERICA - HORN OF AFRICA RISK TRANSFER FOR ADAPTATION ETHIOPIAN PROJECT, 2009-2014; 2 folders (Box R4446)
  - INV, 2012-2014; AC_2015_018_11; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2012 INV 301 - PHILANTHROPY NORTHWEST - EXPANSION OF PRI MAKERS NETWORKS EDUCATION AND TRAINING PROGRAMS, 2012-2013 (Box R4446)
    - 2012 INV 303 - PAN-AFRICAN UNIVERSITY (NIGERIA) - IMPACT INVESTING POLICY PROJECT, 2012-2014 (Box R4446)
    - 2012 INV 304 - AFRICAN VENTURE CAPITAL ASSOCIATION (ENGLAND) - IMPACT INVESTING IN AFRICA, 2012-2014 (Box R4446)
    - 2012 INV 305 - DALBERG CONSULTING - IMPACT INVESTING IN SENEGAL, 2012-2013 (Box R4446)
    - 2012 INV 306 - IMPACT INVESTMENT SHUJOG LTD. (SINGAPORE) - GENERAL SUPPORT, 2012-2013 (Box R4446)
    - 2012 INV 307 - VENTURE CAPITAL TRUST FUND (GHANA) - IMPACT INVESTING POLICY RESEARCH, 2012-2013 (Box R4446)
    - 2012 INV 308 - STRATHMORE UNIVERSITY (KENYA) - POLICY FOR IMPACT INVESTING, 2012-2014 (Box R4446)
    - 2012 INV 309 - FUNDACION SISTEMA B (CHILE) - GENERAL SUPPORT (Box R4446)
    - 2012 INV 310 - ViLCAP - GENERAL SUPPORT, 2012-2013 (Box R4446)
    - 2012 INV 311 - MISSION HUB - SOCIAL CAPITAL MARKETS CONFERENCE 2012 (Box R4446)
    - 2012 INV 312 - ASIA COMMUNITY VENTURES (HONG KONG) - PROJECT ENGAGEHK 2.0, 2012-2014 (Box R4446)
    - 2012 INV 316 - AVINA AMERICAS - LATIN AMERICAN IMPACT INVESTING FORUM AND FUND, 2012-2013 (Box R4446)
    - 2012 INV 318 - FUNDACION AVINA(PANAMA) - LATIN AMERICAN IMPACT INVESTING FORUM IN BRAZIL, 2012-2013 (Box R4446)
- AC.2015.037: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1980-2015; 2000-2014; 9.2 Cubic Feet Seven standard record storage boxes, R4447-R4453.
  - INV, 2011-2013; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2012 INV 319 - IMPACTASSETS, INC. - SYNTHETIC SEED FUND, 2012-2013 (Box R4447)
    - 2012 INV 321 - NORTHWESTERN UNIVERSITY - 2013 INTERNATIONAL IMPACT INVESTING CHALLENGE, 2011-2013 (Box R4447)
    - 2012 INV 324 - MONITOR COMPANY GROUP - IMPACT INVESTING CONVENINGS FACILITATION, 2012-2013 (Box R4447)
  - ISS, 2011-2014; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2012 ISS 301 - ALLIANCE FOR A GREEN REVOLUTION IN AFRICA (KENYA) - GREEN REVOLUTION FORUM, TANZANIA 2012, 2012-2013 (Box R4447)
    - 2012 ISS 302 - GLOBAL KNOWLEDGE INITIATIVE - AFRICA COLLABORATION COLLOQUIUM ON FOOD SECURITY, 2012-2013 (Box R4447)
    - 2012 ISS 306 - METROPOLITAN AREA RESEARCH CORPORATION - BUILDING ONE AMERICA CAMPAIGN, 2011-2013 (Box R4447)
    - 2012 ISS 307 - CENTRE FOR DEVELOPMENT AND ENTERPRISE (SOUTH AFRICA) - URBANIZATION'S IMPACT ON YOUTH UNEMPLOYMENT IN SOUTH AFRICA, BRAZIL AND INDIA, 2012-2014 (Box R4447)
    - 2012 ISS 308 - GSMA FOUNDATION - MOBILE AND DEVELOPMENT INTELLIGENCE PROGRAM, 2012-2013 (Box R4447)
    - 2012 ISS 309 - STANFORD UNIVERSITY - MEASURING THE IMPACT OF INFRASTRUCTURE DEVELOPMENT ON ECOSYSTEM SERVICES, 2012-2014 (Box R4447)
    - 2012 ISS 311 - ROYAL INSTITUTE OF INTERNATIONAL AFFAIRS (ENGLAND) - MOVING TOWARD UNIVERSAL HEALTH COVERAGE, 2012-2014 (Box R4447)
    - 2012 ISS 313 - KASETSART UNIVERSITY(THAILAND) -10TH INTERNATIONAL SYMPOSIUM ON RICE FUNCTIONAL GENOMICS, 2012-2014 (Box R4447)
    - 2012 ISS 316 - DALBERG GLOBAL DEVELOPMENT ADVISORS KENYA LTD - AGRICULTURAL DEVELOPMENT IN SOUTH SUDAN, 2012-2014 (Box R4447)
    - 2012 ISS 318 - POLICYLINK - U.S. CONVENING ON MORE EQUITABLE GROWTH, 2012-2013 (Box R4447)
  - New York City (NYC), 2012-2014; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 record storage boxes
    - 2012 NYC 304 - RESTAURANT OPPORTUNITIES CENTER OF NEW YORK - DOCUMENTARY ABOUT THE CHALLENGES OF RESTAURANT WORKERS, 2012-2014 (Box R4447)
    - 2012 NYC 305 - ALLIANCE OF RESIDENT THEATRES - DEVELOPING A NEW MODEL FOR NON-PROFIT ARTS ORGANIZATIONS, 2012-2014 (Box R4447)
    - 2012 NYC 306 - APOLLO THEATER FOUNDATION - LEVERAGE BRAND TO SECURE SUSTAINABLE EARNED-INCOME, 2012-2014 (Box R4447)
    - 2012 NYC 311 - GHETTO FILM SCHOOL - DEVELOP STUDENTS' CREATIVE VIDEO PRODUCTION SKILLS, 2012-2014 (Box R4447)
    - 2012 NYC 313 - THE LAUNDROMAT PROJECT - ART WORKSHOPS IN LOCAL COIN-OPERATED LAUNDROMATS, 2012-2014 (Box R4447)
    - 2012 NYC 314 - MAPP INTERNATIONAL PRODUCTIONS - FESTIVAL OF LIFE'S WORK OF SEKOU SUNDIATA, 2012-2014 (Box R4447)
    - 2015:037:001 - Blink Your Eyes Sekou Sundiata Revisited, 2015:037:001; Published material. (Box R4447)
    - 2012 NYC 316 - THE NEW SCHOOL - DEVELOP NYC'S RESIDENTS INTO CO-DESIGNERS OF HPD'S SERVICES, 2012-2014 (Box R4447)
    - 2015:037:002 - Public & Collaborative - Designing Services for Housing, 2015:037:002; Published material. (Box R4447)
    - 2012 NYC 318 - ST. ANN'S WAREHOUSE, INC. - AMERICAN PREMIERE OF "ROADKILL", 2012-2014 (Box R4448)
    - 2012 NYC 319 - WOMEN'S HOUSING AND ECONOMIC DEVELOPMENT CORP. - PROGRAMMING AND PREDEVELOPMENT OF BRONX MUSIC HERITAGE CENTER, 2012-2014 (Box R4448)
    - 2012 NYC 323 - COMMONWISE EDUCATION - BRONX COOPERATIVE DEVELOPMENT INITIATIVE, 2012-2013 (Box R4448)
    - 2012 NYC 324 - FUND FOR THE CITY OF NEW YORK - THE BROWNSVILLE VIOLENCE REDUCTION INITIATIVE, 2012-2014 (Box R4448)
    - 2012 NYC 325 - MUNICIPAL ART SOCIETY OF NEW YORK - SURVEY ON LIVABILITY IN NEW YORK CITY AND THE MAS SUMMIT, 2012-2013 (Box R4448)
    - 2012 NYC 327 - EMCARTS - INNOVATION SUMMIT FOR THE ARTS, 2012-2014 (Box R4448)
    - 2012 NYC 328 - BROOKLYN ALLIANCE - MAYORAL CANDIDATE FORUM ON EMPLOYER ENGAGEMENT AND TRAINING, 2012-2014 (Box R4448)
    - 2012 NYC 329 - HELICON COLLABORATIVE - EVALUATION OF THE CULTURAL INNOVATION FUND, 2012-2014 (Box R4448)
    - 2015:037:009 - Evaluation of the Cultural Innovation Fund, 2015:037:009; Digital (Box R4448)
      Open for research. Digital access copy currently unavailable. Please contact a RAC archivist for further instruction.
  - OAF, 2010-2014; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2012 OAF 302 - FARM CONCERN INTERNATIONAL (KENYA) - EXPAND YOUTH PARTICIPATION IN AGRICULTURAL SYSTEMS, 2010-2013 (Box R4448)
    - 2012 OAF 303 - AFRICA HEALTH AND DEVELOPMENT INTERNATIONAL - YOUTH CONFERENCE ON PEACE, KENYA FALL 2012, 2012-2013 (Box R4448)
    - 2012 OAF 304- AFRICA CANCER FOUNDATION (KENYA) - RESEARCHING CANCER CASES AND DIAGNOSTIC FACILITIES IN KENYA, 2012-2014 (Box R4448)
    - 2012 OAF 304- AFRICA CANCER FOUNDATION (KENYA) - RESEARCHING CANCER CASES AND DIAGNOSTIC FACILITIES IN KENYA - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 2012-2013 (Box R4480A)
    - 2012 OAF 306 - AFRICAN CENTER FOR ECONOMIC TRANSFORMATION - AFRICAN FUTURES ROUNDTABLE EVENT IN LAGOS, NIGERIA, 2012-2013 (Box R4448)
    - 2012 OAF 307 - UNIVERSITY OF GHANA - 3RD ANNUAL CONFERENCE FOR SCHOOLS OF PUBLIC HEALTH, 2012-2013 (Box R4448)
  - OAS, 2011-2014; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2012 OAS 302 - MAHIDOL UNIVERSITY (THAILAND) - SCHOLARSHIPS TO ATTEND 2012 BIENNIAL ASIAN POPULATION CONFERENCE (Box R4448)
    - 2012 OAS 303 - INDIAN INSTITUTE FOR HUMAN SETTLEMENTS (INDIA) - SAN-KRANTI STUDENT CHALLENGE, 2012-2013 (Box R4448)
    - 2012 OAS 307 - ENERGIZE THE CHAIN - IMPACT OF MOBILE TOWER-LINKED REFRIGERATION ON VACCINE QUALITY IN INDIA, 2011-2014 (Box R4448)
  - OPP, 2011-2013; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 record storage boxes
    - 2012 OPP 301 - MUSEUM OF MODERN ART - "FORECLOSED: REHOUSING THE AMERICAN DREAM," EXHIBITION, PUBLICATION AND EDUCATION PROGRAM, 2011-2012 (Box R4448)
    - 2012 OPP 302 - MUSEUM OF THE CITY OF NEW YORK - "THE GREATEST GRID" EXHIBITION, 2011-2012 (Box R4448)
    - 2012 OPP 304 - MUNICIPAL ART SOCIETY OF NEW YORK - REVIEW PANEL FOR "VIBRANCY INDICATORS" (Box R4449)
    - 2012 OPP 305 - CEC STUYVESANT COVE INC - EQUIP NEW YORK CITY HIGH SCHOOL STUDENTS WITH GREEN JOB SKILLS, 2012-2013 (Box R4449)
  - OSF, 2012-2014; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2012 OSF 305 - GLOBALGIVING FOUNDATION - GENERAL SUPPORT, 2012-2013 (Box R4449)
    - 2012 OSF 312 - JAZZ AT LINCOLN CENTER - GENERAL SUPPORT, 2012-2014 (Box R4449)
  - PHS, 1980-2014; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 record storage boxes
    - 2012 PHS 307 - TIDES CENTER - AGAG PROJECT WORKING WITH AFRICAN INSTITUTIONS, 2004-2013 (Box R4449)
    - 2012 PHS 310 - NEW YORK REGIONAL ASSOCIATION OF GRANTMAKERS - GENERAL SUPPORT, 1980-2014; 4 folders. (Box R4449)
    - 2012 PHS 312 - ORGANISATION FOR ECONOMIC CO-OPERATION AND DEVELOPMENT - GLOBAL NETWORK OF FOUNDATIONS, 2012-2013 (Box R4450)
    - 2012 PHS 313 - AFRICAN FOUNDATION FOR DEVELOPMENT (ENGLAND) - DEVELOP A GIVING PLATFORM FOR YOUNG DIASPORA AFRICANS, 2012-2014 (Box R4450)
    - 2012 PHS 317 - SOUTHERN AFRICA TRUST - GROWING AFRICAN PHILANTHROPY, 2012-2014 (Box R4450)
    - 2012 PHS 320 - CLINTON GLOBAL INITIATIVE - 2012 ANNUAL CONFERENCE, 2012-2013 (Box R4450)
  - POS, 2011-2014; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2012 POS 301 - UNITED STATES AGENCY FOR INTERNATIONAL DEVELOPMENT - "FRONTIERS IN DEVELOPMENT" CONFERENCE, 2011-2012 (Box R4450)
    - 2012 POS 302 - GLOBAL CAMPAIGN FOR CLIMATE ACTION (CANADA) - "WIN A DATE WITH HISTORY", RIO PLUS 20 YOUTH CONTEST (Box R4450)
    - 2012 POS 304 - THE NEW SCHOOL - OCCUPY WALL STREET CONVENINGS, WASHINGTON, DC AND NEW YORK, NY (Box R4450)
    - 2012 POS 305 - INTERNATIONAL INSTITUTE FOR ENVIRONMENT AND DEVELOPMENT - RIO PLUS 20 UNITED NATIONS CONFERENCE, 2012-2013 (Box R4450)
    - 2012 POS 306 - AVINA FOUNDATION (PANAMA) - FORUM OF SOCIAL ENTREPRENEURSHIP IN THE NEW ECONOMY, BRAZIL 2012 (Box R4450)
    - 2012 POS 307 - UNITED NATIONS ENTITY FOR GENDER EQUALITY AND THE EMPOWERMENT OF WOMEN - RIO PLUS 20 AND RURAL WOMEN FEED AFRICA, 2012-2013 (Box R4450)
    - 2015:037:003 - UN Women 80851-83119 R10, R20 Annexes, 2015:037:003; Digital (Box R4450)
    - 2012 POS 308 - SHOW OF FORCE - "HALF THE SKY" PROJECT, 2012-2013 (Box R4450)
    - 2015:037:004-005 - Half the Sky, 2015:037:004; Digital (Box R4450)
    - 2012 POS 309 - SUSTAINABILITY ACCOUNTING STANDARDS BOARD - GENERAL SUPPORT, 2012-2014 (Box R4450)
    - 2012 POS 311 - GLOBAL ENVIRONMENT AND TECHNOLOGY FOUNDATION - U.S. WATER PARTNERSHIP, 2012-2013 (Box R4450)
  - PRD, 2009-2013; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 record storage boxes
    - 2012 PRD 201 - WILLIAM DAVIDSON INSTITUTE AT THE UNIVERSITY OF MICHIGAN - IMPACT SOURCING FOR JOB CREATION OPPORTUNITIES, 2012-2013 (Box R4450)
    - 2012 PRD 202 - MONITOR COMPANY GROUP LP - SCALING IMPACT SOURCING, 2012-2013 (Box R4450)
    - 2012 PRD 203 - HICHERT and ASSOCIATES (SOUTH AFRICA) - THE FUTURE OF IMPACT SOURCING (Box R4450)
    - 2012 PRD 204 - UNIVERSITY OF KWAZULU-NATAL (SOUTH AFRICA) - LABOR MARKET ANALYSIS FOR GHANA, KENYA AND SOUTH AFRICA, 2012-2013 (Box R4450)
    - 2012 PRD 205 - GLOBAL SOURCING COUNCIL - 2012 3S AWARDS HONORING IMPACT SOURCING, 2012-2013 (Box R4450)
    - 2012 PRD 206 - IKHONO COMMUNICATIONS (SOUTH AFRICA) - IMPACT SOURCING GRANTEE CONVENING - COALITION BUILDING, 2011-2012 (Box R4451)
    - 2015:037:006 - Gala Dinner, 2015:037:006; Digital (Box R4451)
    - 2015:037:007-008 - Conference Part 1 and 2, 2015:037:007; Digital (Box R4451)
    - 2012 PRD 207 - DIGITAL DIVIDE DATA - DOCUMENTING MODELS FOR PROVIDING SKILLS TRAINING AND EMPLOYMENT OPPORTUNITIES IN THE BPO SECTOR, 2009-2013 (Box R4451)
    - 2012 PRD 208 - ACCENTURE LLP - CORPORATE CARVE OUT, 2011-2013 (Box R4451)
    - 2012 PRD 209 - INTERNATIONAL YOUTH FOUNDATION - COMPARTIVE ANALYSIS OF OPPORTUNITIES FOR YOUTH EMPLOYMENT IN AFRICA, 2012-2013 (Box R4451)
    - 2012 PRD 210 - HUNGRY HEART MEDIA - IMPACT SOURCING VIDEO (Box R4451)
    - 2012 PRD 211 - RESULTS FOR DEVELOPMENT INSTITUTE - INNOVATIVE SECONDARY EDUCATION FOR SKILL ENHANCEMENT, 2011-2013 (Box R4451)
  - PRE, 2012-2013; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2012 PRE 301 - GREATER WASHINGTON EDUCATIONAL TELECOMMUNICATIONS ASSOCIATION - PBS NEWSHOUR, 2012-2013 (Box R4451)
    - 2012 PRE 302 - THE NEW SCHOOL - HOUSING POLICY IN THE US AND UK, 2012-2013 (Box R4451)
    - 2012 PRE 306 - AMERICAS SOCIETY - RENOVATION TO HONOR DAVID ROCKEFELLER (Box R4451)
  - RES, 2009-2014; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 record storage boxes
    - 2012 RES 301 - STRATEGIC FORESIGHT GROUP (INDIA) - TREND MONITORING AND HORIZON SCANNING IN ASIA, 2009-2013 (Box R4451)
    - 2012 RES 303 - FORO NACIONAL INTERNACIONAL (PERU) - TREND MONITORING AND HORIZON SCANNING IN SOUTH AMERICA, 2009-2014 (Box R4451)
    - 2012 RES 304 - INTELLECAP - RESEARCH PRODUCTS TO REDUCE POVERTY IN GLOBAL SOUTH, 2011-2013 (Box R4451)
    - 2012 RES 306 - INSTITUTE FOR THE FUTURE - ANALYSIS OF SEARCHLIGHT NEWSLETTERS, 2010-2012 (Box R4451)
    - 2015:037:010 - Oversized Posters, 2015:037:010; Oversize (Ephemera) (Roll 1)
    - 2012 RES 307 - NATIONAL SCIENCE TECHNOLOGY AND INNOVATION POLICY OFFICE (THAILAND) - ASEAN-KRABI INITIATIVE, 2012-2014 (Box R4452)
    - 2012 RES 308 - BERLIN CIVIL SOCIETY CENTER (GERMANY) - THE FUTURE OF CIVIL SOCIETY ORGANIZATIONS - PROMOTING THE GLOBAL DEBATE, 2012-2013 (Box R4452)
    - 2012 RES 309 - UNITED NATIONS EDUCATIONAL, SCIENTIFIC AND CULTURAL ORGANIZATION - GLOBAL NETWORK OF UNESCO FUTURES CENTERS BELLAGIO CONVENING, 2012-2014 (Box R4452)
  - RLC, 2012-2014; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2012 RLC 303 - AMERICAN NATIONAL RED CROSS - STRENGTHENING COLLABORATION ON DISASTER PREPAREDNESS, 2012-2014 (Box R4452)
    - 2012 RLC 304 - LUND UNIVERSITY (SWEDEN) - METHODOLOGIES TO MEASURE AND STRENGTHEN COMMUNITY RESILIENCE, 2012-2014 (Box R4452)
    - 2012 RLC 305 - ENVIRONMENTAL DEFENSE FUND - COASTAL LOUISIANA DESIGN INITIATIVE, 2012-2014 (Box R4452)
  - SEG, 2009-2015; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 record storage boxes
    - 2012 SEG 201 - INNOVATION NETWORK FOR COMMUNITIES - DEVELOPING SUSTAINABLE WATER MARKETS, 2012-2013 (Box R4452)
    - 2012 SEG 202 - M and R STRATEGIC SERVICES, INC.- COMMUNICATIONS CAMPAIGN FOR GREEN JOBS, 2012-2013 (Box R4452)
    - 2012 SEG 203 - LOS ANGELES ALLIANCE FOR A NEW ECONOMY - WASTE MANAGEMENT DEMONSTRATION PROJECT, 2012-2013 (Box R4452)
    - 2012 SEG 204 - PESTICIDE ACTION NETWORK NORTH AMERICA - IMPLEMENTATION OF RECYCLING AS A GREEN JOBS SOLUTION, 2012-2013 (Box R4452)
    - 2012 SEG 205 - NATURE CONSERVANCY - WATER INFRASTRUCTURE FINANCING IN PHILADELPHIA, 2012-2013 (Box R4452)
    - 2012 SEG 206 - ABT ASSOCIATES - EVALUATION OF SUSTAINABLE EMPLOYMENT IN A GREEN US ECONOMY (SEGUE), 2011-2013 (Box R4452)
    - 2012 SEG 207 - NATIONAL EMPLOYMENT LAW PROJECT, INC - GOOD JOBS FOR A SUSTAINABLE ECONOMY PROJECT, 2012-2013 (Box R4452)
    - 2012 SEG 208 - THE ENERGY FOUNDATION - RETROFIT SEGMENTATION ANALYSIS, 2012-2014 (Box R4452)
    - 2012 SEG 209 - CENTER FOR AMERICAN PROGRESS - "A NEW VISION FOR AMERICA" PROJECT, 2012-2014 (Box R4453)
    - 2012 SEG 210 - OREGON STATE TREASURY - WEST COAST INFRASTRUCTURE EXCHANGE, 2011-2015 (Box R4453)
      Restricted - Open in 2025
    - 2012 SEG 211 - GREEN FOR AL- GENERAL OPERATING SUPPORT, 2012-2014 (Box R4453)
    - 2012 SEG 212 - EMERALD CITIES PARTNERSHIP - GREENING STRATEGIES, 2009-2013 (Box R4453)
    - 2012 SEG 213 - PROGRESSIVE AMERICA FUND - GENERAL SUPPORT, 2012-2013 (Box R4453)
    - 2012 SEG 214 - PARTNERSHIP FOR WORKING FAMILIES - CORE SUPPORT, 2012-2014 (Box R4453)
    - 2012 SEG 215 - CLEAN ENERGY WORKS OREGON - GENERAL SUPPORT, 2012-2014 (Box R4453)
    - 2012 SEG 216 - BLUEGREEN ALLIANCE FOUNDATION - GENERAL SUPPORT, 2012-2014 (Box R4453)
  - SRC, 2012-2014; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2012 SRC 101 - MONITOR COMPANY GROUP - LANDSCAPE RESEARCH OF DONOR ACTIVITY IN IMPACT ENTERPRISES (Box R4453)
    - 2012 SRC 103 - FSG INC. - SHARED VALUE MEASUREMENT RESEARCH (Box R4453)
    - 2012 SRC 104 - NONPROFIT ENTERPRISE AND SELF-SUSTAINABILITY TEAM - RESEARCH ON ENABLING ENVIRONMENTS FOR CREATING IMPACT, 2012-2013 (Box R4453)
    - 2012 SRC 105 - WILLIAM DAVIDSON INSTITUTE, AT THE UNIVERSITY OF MICHIGAN - GLOBAL CONCEPTS OF IMPACT ENTERPRISES, 2012-2013 (Box R4453)
    - 2012 SRC 106 - FSG, INC. - CAPTURE LEARNING FROM OUTPUTS OF RF EXPLORATIONS, 2012-2013 (Box R4453)
    - 2012 SRC 107 - IRC INTERNATIONAL WATER AND SANITATION CENTER (NETHERLANDS) - BC CONFERENCE - WATER MULTIPLE USE SYSTEMS ROUNDTABLE, 2012-2013 (Box R4453)
    - 2012 SRC 108 - BUSINESS FOR SOCIAL RESPONSIBILITY- PRIVATE SECTOR IDEA GENERATION, 2012-2014 (Box R4453)
    - 2012 SRC 109 - COLUMBIA UNIVERSI TY - STUDY THE INTERFACE OF FORMAL AND INFORMAL TRANSIT IN NAIROBI, KENYA, 2012-2014 (Box R4453)
    - 2012 SRC 110 - UNIVERSITY OF NAIROBI (KENYA) - STUDY THE INTERFACE OF FORMAL AND INFORMAL TRANSIT IN NAIROBI, 2012-2013 (Box R4453)